In the fragment detailed layout, a text view
is already defined. We have to assign it an
ID so that within the detail fragment of detail
activity we can use find view by ID to
find the text view. To determine the forecast
info that the text view should display. We can
access the intent that the detail activity was launched
by. We're going to use this inside of onCreateView.
[SOUND] Since we added an intent extra with the forecast
data there. We can read that intent extra back to display in the text
view, as you can see we pulled the forecast string from the
intent find our rootView and then set the text to that forecast string